回到Rato所说，frame布局、linear布局、relative布局，
Going back to what Rato said, frame layout, linear layout, and relative layout
这三种布局将会是你在构建UI时最常遇见的。
are three of the most common layouts you will use in building out your UI.
这些都继承自view group类，是用来包容和排列里面的子视图（各种view）的。
These all descend from the view group class, designed to contain and
每一种布局都有各自的优势，
give order to child views. They each have their strengths and
你应该尝试学习使用他们，尽量用最简单的布局完成工作
you should always try to use this simplest layout that will get the job done.
Frame Layout（框架布局）非常适合简单的布局，当你只有一个子视图时，
Frame Layout is great for simple layouts when you only have one child to view,
例如内容区域只有列表视图的情况。
like a list view that fills the entire content area. Linear layout is
Linear Layout（线性布局）能够使子视图水平或垂直排列
perfect for stacking the views vertically or horizontally, one after another,
它也是唯一一个能够打破比例显示的布局
it is also the only way to break up the display proportionately. Relative layout
Relative Layout相较于别的布局来说更为强大，当然也更为复杂。
is powerful but a bit more complicated compared to the others. Throw a bunch of
你可以相对于其父元素的位置来设置其中的子元素的位置
views inside a relative layout, and then you can configure each views
也可以相对它的同级别元素的位置来设置，这就是“相对”布局
position relative to parent, the relative layout, or to sibling views, tons of
当我们构建更复杂的UI时，我们会更加详细的讨论布局。
possibilities. We'll explore these layouts in greater detail when we build more
现在让我们来设计我们的天气预报列表
complex screens. For now, let's get back to building our forecast list.